Guide to the Baldwin Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Fowler, William Worthington, 1833-1881
Frazine, George Nelson, 1860-1902
French, Joseph Richardson, 1836-1913
Frisbie, Samuel Hanna, 1840-1907
Fukushima, Katsutoro, 1865-1936
Galatti, Pantoleon G., 1809-1896
Galatti, Stephen G., 1808-1876
Gavigan, Edward James, 1864-1943
Gerry, Elbridge Thomas, 1837-1927
Gibbs, George, 1815-1873
Gibbs, Henry, 1749-1794
Giddings, Van Renssalaer Canfield, 1833-Â
Gifford, Ellen (Marett), 1815-1889
Giles, William Alexander, 1836-1913
Gillette, Charles William, 1831-Â
Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1831-1908
Gilman, Warren, Randall, 1861-1920
Gilmore, James Roberts, 1822-1903
Godard, George Seymour, 1865-Â
Goddard, Calvin, 1768-1842
Gold, Theodore Sedgwick, 1818-1906
Goodale, Wilmot Hinks, 1839-1897
Goodnow, Frank Johnson, 1859-1939
Goodrich, Chauncey Allen, 1790-1860
Goodrich, Elizur, 1761-1849
Goodrich, Julia Frances (Webster), 1793-1869
Gornings, Henry Honeychurch, 1841-1885
Gould, Edward Sherman, 1808-1885
Gould, James, 1770-1838
Granger, Francis, 1792-1868
Granger, Gideon, 1821-1868
Granger, Miles Tobey, 1817-1895
Granger, Ralph, 1790-1843
Groves, Charles Alfred, 1850-1928
Gray, John Chipman, 1839-1915
Greene, Daniel Crosby, 1843-1913
Greene, Roger Sherman, 1840-1930
Greene, Thomas Casey, 1826-1897
Gregory, Charles Noble, 1851-1932
Griswold, Benjamin, 1811-1844
Griswold, Jared, 1794-1835
Griswold, Stanley, 1764-1815
Grosvenor, Edwin Augustus, 1845-1936
Gross, Charles Edward, 1847-1924
Gulick, Sidney Lewis, 1860-1945
Gunn, George Miles, 1851-1926
Hadley, Arthur Twining, 1856-1930
Hadley, James, 1821-1872
Hagerman, James, 1848-Â
Hale, Edward Everett, 1822-1909
Hall, Eli Edwin, 1814-1896
Hall, Frederic Byron, 1843-1913
Hall, Thomas Seavey, 1827-1880
Hall, William Kitteridge, 1836-1906
Halsey, Jeremiah, 1832-Â
Hamersley, William, 1838-1920
Hamilton, John Church, 1792-1882
Hammond, John Hays, 1855-1936
Hammond, William Gardiner, 1829-1894
Hanford, Cornelius Holgate, 1849-Â
Haradon, Amasa Franklin, 1837-1909
Harding, Chester, 1792-1866
Hardy, Alpheus Holmes, Â -1917
Harlan, John Marshall, 1833-1911
Harris, William Torrey, 1835-1909
Harrison, Carter Henry, 1860-Â
Harrison, Charles Custis, 1844-1929
Harrison, Henry Baldwin, 1821-1901
Harrison, Lynde, 1837-1906
Hart, Albert Bushnell, 1854-1943
Hart, Hastings Hornell, 1851-Â
Hart, Samuel, 1845-1917
Hatoyama, Kasuo, 1856-1911
Hawley, Joseph Roswell, 1826-1905
Head, John Frazier, 1821-1908
Herrick, Samuel Edwards, 1841-1904
Higgins, Anthony, 1840-1912
Higginson, Stephen, 1743-1828
Higginson, Thomas Wentworth, 1823-1911
Hill, David Jayne, 1850-1932
Hillhouse, Augustus Lucas, 1791-1859
Hillhouse, James, 1754-1832
Hillhouse, James, 1854-1938
Hillhouse, James Abraham, 1789-1841
Hillyer, Charles Tudor, 1800-Â
Hinckley, Henry Rose, 1838-1918
Hinkley, Edward Otis, 1824-1896
Hinkley, John, 1864-1940
Hinman, Joel, 1802-1870
Hitchcock, Ernest, 1856-Â
Hitchcock, Henry, 1829-1902
Hoar, Ebenezer Rockwood, 1816-1895
Hoar, George Frisbie, 1826-1904
Hoar, Samuel, 1778-1856
Hodges, Edward Tuller, 1816-1883
Holland, Thomas Erskine, 1835-1926
Holls, George Frederick William, 1857-1903
Holmes, Jabez Silas, Â -1884
Holmes, Oliver Wendell, 1841-1935
Holt, Henry, 1840-1926
Hooker, John, 1816-1901
Hoppin, James Mason, 1820-1906
Hoppin, William Warner, Â -1913
Hornblower, William Butler, 1851-1914
Horne, Charles Francis, 1870-1942
Hosmer, Stephen Titus, 1763-1834
Hotchkiss, Justus Street, 1831-1915
Hough, Isaac Insign, 1781-1852
Houston, John Wallace, 1814-1896
Howe, William Wirt, 1833-1909
Howells, William Dean, 1837-1920
Howry, Charles Bowen, 1844-1928
Hubbard, Nehemiah, 1752-1837
Hubbard, Samuel Dickinson, 1799-1855
Hubbard, Stephen Crosvenor, 1816-1905
Hunt, Carleton, 1836-1921
Huntington, Ebenezer, 1754-1834
Huntington, Jabez Williams, 1788-1847
Huntington, Henry William, 1789-1854
Hyde, Alvan Pinney, 1825-1894
Hyde, Charles Cheney, 1873-Â
Ingersoll, Charles Roberts, 1821-1903
Ingersoll, George Pratt, 1861-1927
Ingersoll, Henry Hulbert, Â -1915
Ingersoll, Ralph Isaacs, 1789-1872
Iredell, James, 1751-1799
Ives, Brayton, 1840-1914
Ives, Charles Linneaus, 1831-1879
Ives, Isaac, 1764-1845
Ives, Nathan Beers, 1806-1869
Jackson, Andrew, Pres. U.S.? 1767-1845
James, Benjamin Franklin, 1863-1935
Jameson, John Franklin, 1859-1937
Jamieson, William D., 1873-1949
Jamis, Isaac, 1738-1812
Jamis, Leonard Augustus, 1832-1909
Jamis, Luther Manard, 1837-1921
Jamis, Samuel Finley, 1826-Â
Jarves, James Jackson, 1818-1888
Jarvis, Richard William Hart, 1829-1903
Jefferson, Thomas, Pres. U.S., 1743-1826
Jenkins, Jonathan Leavitt, 1830-1913
Jenks, Jeremiah Whipple, 1856-1929
Jewett, Pliny Adams, 1816-1884
Jocelyn, Nathaniel, 1796-1881
Jocelyn, Simeon Smith, 1799-1879
Johnson, Reverdy, 1796-1876
Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1853-1937
Johnson, William Samuel, 1882-Â
Johnston, Henry Phelps, 1842-1923
Jones, Leonard Augustus, 1832-1909
Joslyn, Charles Mason, 1849-Â
Joy, Charles Arad, 1823-1891
Joy, James Richard, 1863-1957
Judson, Andrew Thompson, 1784-1853
Judson, David, 1757-1841
Judson, Frederick Newton, 1845-1919
Judson, Philander, Â -1806
Kelloggs, Herbert Humphrey, 1872-1934
Kelloggs, Stephen Wright, 1822-1904
Kendall, William Sergeant, 1869-1938
Kennedy, Joseph Camp Griffith, 1813-1887
Kennedy, William, 1854-1918
Kent, James, 1763-1847
Kent, William, 1802-1861
Kimberley, Dennis, 1790-1862
King, James Gore, 1791-1853
Kingsbury, Frederick John, 1823-1910
Kingsbury, George Henry, 1827-1899
Kingsbury, Henry, 1801-1889
Kingsley, Henry Coit, 1815-1886
Kinney, John Coddington, 1793-1891
Kirby, Ephraim, 1757-1804
Kirkland, Charles Pinckney, 1798-1883
Kitchel, Cornelius Ladd, 1841-1929
Klein, Jacob, 1845-1910
Knevals, Sherman Willard, 1832-1908
Knickerbocker, Herman, 1779-1855
Knox, Philander Chase, 1853-1921
Komatzu, Midori, 1867-1942
Kurahara, Koreteru, 1874-1933
Langdon, Timothy, 1758-1801
Lanman, Charles Rockwell, 1850-1941
Lanman, James, 1769-1841
Lansing, Garret Yates, 1783-1862
Larned, Irene (Battell), 1811-1877
Lathrop, John, 1740-1816
Law, Lyman, 1770-1816
Law, Richard, 1733-1806
Law, Samuel Andrew, 1771-1845
Law, William Henry, 1803-1881
Lawler, Daniel William, 1859-1926
Lawson, John Davidson, 1852-1921
Lawton, Alexander Robert, 1818-1896
Learned, Walter, 1847-1915
Leavenworth, Mar, 1752-1812
Leavitt, Joshua, 1794-1873
Lewis, John, 1746-1792
Lewis, William Draper, 1867-1949
Lines, Edwin Stevens, 1845-1927
Linsley, Sophia Brainard (Lyon), 1782-1866
Littlefield, Charles Edgar, 1851-1915
Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1850-1924
Lorring, Charles Creeley, 1794-1867
Lounsbury, Phineas Chapman, 1841-1925
Lovett, John Erskine, 1794-1847
Ludlow, Henry Gilbert, 1797-1867
Lurton, Horace Harnam, 1844-1914
Lyman, Jonathan, 1737-1766
McClain, Emlin, 1851-1915
McCrady, Edward, 1802-1892
McCue, Thomas Patrick, 1867-1947
McCurdy, Charles Johnson, 1797-1891
McKinney, Edward Pascal, 1838-1925
Mackintosh, Frank Harbottle, 1864-1939
McLane, Louis, 1786-1857
McLean, George Payne, 1857-1932
McMaster, John Bach, 1852-1932
MacVeagh, Isaac Wayne, 1833-1917
Madison, James, Pres. Of U.S.? 1751-1836
Marcy, William Learned, 1786-1857
Marett, Phillip, 1792-1869
Marsh, Othniel Charles, 1831-1899
Marshall, Thomas Riley, 1854-1925
Marvin, Edwin Elinhalet, 1833-Â
Masao, Tokichi, 1870-1921
Mason, Edward Gay, 1839-1898
Mather, John Perkins Gushing, 1816-1891
Matsukata, Kojiro, 1866-1950
Matteson, Charles, 1840-1925
Mead, Charles Marsh, 1836-1911
Mead, Edwin Doak, 1849-1937
Mead, Frederick, 1848-1918
Mead, John Abner, 1841-1920
Meigs, Josiah, 1757-1822
Melville, Herman, 1819-1891
Meredith, William Morris, 1799-1873
Merwin, Samuel, 1781-1856
Mills, William Henry, 1805-1897
Mitchell, Charles LeMoyne, 1844-1890
Mitchell, Donald Grant, 1822-1908
Mitchell, Justus, 1754-1806
Mitchell, Stephen Mix, 1743-1835
Monson, Levinus, 1791-1859
Moody, Dwight Lyman, 1837-1899
Moore, Edward Cadwell, 1857-1943
Moore, John Bassett, 1860-1947
Moore, Nathaniel Schuyler, 1839-1913
Moran, James Thomas, 1864-1936
Morehead, James Turner, 1797-1854
Morris, John Moses, 1837-1873
Morse, Jedidiah, 1761-1826
Morse, Leonard, 1848-Â
Morse, Richard Cary, 1841-1926
Morse, Sidney Edward, 1794-1871
Morse, Sidney Edwards, 1835-1908
Morton, Thomas Campbell, 1836-1899
Mowry, Elisha Capron, 1836-1899
Munger, Theodore Thornton, 1830-1910
Munson, Cyrus LaRue, 1854-1922
Munson, Harris B. 1821-1885
Munson, Israel, 1767-1844
Murray, John R., 1737-1808
Nelson, Samuel, 1792-1873
Newel, Stanford, 1839-1907
Newton, Susan Maria (Colton), 1831-Â
Newton, William Wilberforece, 1843-1914
Nichols, John Cutler, 1801-1868
Niles, John Milton, 1787-1856
Noel, Edmund Fanor, 1856-Â
Northrop, Cyrus, 1834-1933
Norton, Charles Nedyard, 1837-1909
Noyes, Benjamin, 1816-1891
Noyes, William, Â -1915
Noyes, William Curtis, 1805-1864
O'German, James Aloysius, 1860-1943
Okado, Taiso, 1867-Â
Okubo, Toshitake, 1867-1943
Olmstead, Hawley, 1793-1868
Olmstead, Denison, 1791-1859
Olney, Richard, 1835-1917
Osborne, Norris Galpin, 1858-1932
Osler, Sir William, 1849-1919
Owen, Charles Hunter, 1838-Â
Packard, Lewis Richard, 1836-1884
Page, Carroll Smalley, 1843-1884
Page, James Alfred, Â -1917
Paine, Robert Treat, 1805-1885
Palmer, Charles Ray, 1834-1914
Palmer, Charles Theodore Hart, 1837-1897
Pardee, Dwight Whitfield, 1822-1893
Pardee, Moses Banton, 1821-1892
Park, Charles Ware, 1845-1895
Park, William E., 1837-1910
Parker, Alton Brooks, 1852-1926
Parker, Edwin Pond, 1836-1920
Parker, Isaac, 1768-1830
Parker, Richard Wayne, 1848-1923
Parker, Willard, 1800-1884
Parker, Willard, 1846-Â
Parker, William Belmont, 1871-1934
Parsons, Francis, 1795-1861
Parsons, Isaac, 1790-1868
Parsons, John Caldwell, 1832-1898
Parsons, Theophilus, 1750-1813
Partridge, John Warren, 1843-1889
Peabody, Charles Augustus, 1814-1901
Peabody, George Foster, 1852-1938
Peabody, Olmer William Bourn, 1799-1848
Peck, Bela, 1757-1850
Peck, Elisha, 1790-Â
Peck, Epaphroditus, 1860-1938
Peck, Henry Edwards, 1805-1858
Peck, Tracy, 1838-1921
Peck, William Montrossor, 1853-1927
Peet, Isaac Lewis, Â -1898
Peet, William, 1822-1895
Pelton, George Austin, 1833-1914
Pemberton, James, 1723-1809
Pendleton, George Hunt, 1825-1889
Percival, James Gates, 1795-1856
Peres, Israel Human, 1867-1925
Perkins, Arthur, 1864-1932
Perkins, Bishop, 1787-1866
Perkins, Bishop Walden, 1841-1894
Perkins, Charles Orton, 1819-1887
Perkins, Enoch, 1760-1828
Perkins, Frederick Beecher, 1828-1899
Perkins, George Clap, 1839-1875
Perkins, George William, 1804-1856
Perkins, Henry Augustus, 1801-1874
Perkins, Nathan, 1749-1838
Perkins, Samuel Clarke, 1828-1903
Perkins, Thomas Clap, 1798-1870
Perley, Lyman Ormond, 1866-1931
Perry, Aaron Fyfe, 1815-1893
Perry, John Hoyt, 1848-1928
Peters, Richard, 1780-1848
Peters, Samuel Andrew, 1770-1854
Peters, William Thompson, 1805-1885
Phelps, Charles Pierpont, 1861-1912
Phelps, Edward John, 1822-1900
Phelps, Sylvanus Dryden, 1816-1895
Phelps, William Walter, 1839-1894
Phillips, Andrew Wheeler, 1844-1915
Pierce, Edward Lillie, 1829-1897
Pierce, Franklin, Pres. U.S., 1804-1869
Pierrepont, Edwards, 1817-1892
Pinney, Charles Biddle, 1871-Â
Pitkin, Thomas Clap, 1816-1887
Platt, Henry Clifford, 1832-Â
Platt, James Perry, 1851-1913
Platt, Johnson Tuttle, -1890
Platt, Orville Hitchcock, 1827-1905
Platt, Thomas Collier, 1833-1910
Poland, Luke Potter, 1815-1887
Polk, James Knox, Pres. U.S., 1795-1849
Pomeroy, Hiram Sterling, Â -1917
Pomeroy, John Norton, 1828-1885
Pomeroy, John Norton, 1866-1924
Porter, John Addison, 1856-1900
Porter, Noah, 1811-1892
Porter, Solomon, 1752-1821
Pratt, Julius H., 1791-Â
Prentice, Samuel Oscar, 1850-1924
Prescott, Enos Alling, 1787-1865
Putnam, William Le Baron, 1835-1918
Rawle, Francis, 1846-1930
Raymond, Daniel, 1786-1849
Reeve, Tapping, 1754-1823
Reid, Whitelaw, 1837-1912
Rice, John Strong, 1816-1885
Richardson, Nathaniel Smith, 1810-1883
Ripley, George Coit, 1839-1909
Robbins, Edward Denmore, 1853-1932
Robbins, James Watson, 1782-1847
Robbins, Silas Webster, 1785-1871
Robinson, Edward, 1794-1863
Robinson, Henry Cornelius, 1832-1900
Robinson, William Callyhan, 1834-1911
Robinson, William Erigena, 1814-1892
Rockwell, Charles, 1806-1882
Rockwell, John Arnold, 1803-1861
Rodgers, Christopher Raymond Perry, 1819-1892
Rogers, Benjamin Woolsey, Â -1859
Rogers, Henry Wade, 1853-1926
Root, Alexander Porter, 1840-1908
Root, Charles George, 1855-1928
Root, Elihu, 1845-1937
Root, Ephraim, 1762-1825
Root, Frederick Stanley, 1853-1906
Ropes, John Codman, 1836-1899
Roraback, Alberto T., 1849-1923
Rossiter, Nathaniel, 1762-1835
Roth, Henry Warren, 1838-1918
Russell, Alfred, 1830-1906
Russell, John Edwards, 1834-1903
Russell, Matthew Talcott, 1761-1828
Russell, William Goodwin, Â -1896
Russell, William Huntington, 1809-1885
Ryden, George Herbert, 1884-1941
Sabin, Charles Hamilton, 1868-1933
Salisbury, Edward Elbridge, 1814-1901
Sams, Martha Macon (Minor), Â -1897
Sanborn, Franklin Benjamin, 1831-1917
Sanderson, Joseph, 1823-Â
Sanford, Edward Isaac, 1826-1893
Sanford, Elias Benjamin, 1843-1932
Sanford, Henry Seymour, 1832-1901
Sargent, Henry Bradford, 1851-1927
Sargent, Joseph Bradford, 1822-1907
Sawyer, Rollin Alger, 1861-1925
Sayre, Moses McIlvain, Â -1901
Schouler, James, 1839-1920
Scott, James Brown, 1869-1943
Scranton, Erastus, 1777-1861
Sears, Lorenzo, 1858-1916
Sedgwick, Theodore, 1811-1859
Sedgwick, William Thompson, 1855-1921
Semple, Henry Churchill, 1822-1894
Seward, Clarence Armstrong, 1828-
Seward, William Henry, 1801-1872
Seymour, George Dudley, 1859-1945
Seymour, Origen Storrs, 1804-1881
Shank, Corvin Sheridan, 1866-1947
Sharp, George Matthews, 1851-1911
Shearer, Sextue, 1838-1869
Sheffield, George St. John, 1842-1924
Sheffield, Joseph Earl, 1793-1882
Sheffield, William Paine, 1819-1907
Sheldon, Winthrop Dudley, 1839-1931
Sheppard, Morris, 1875-1941
Sherman, Charles Phineas, 1874-Â
Sherman, Frank Dempster, 1860-1916
Sherman, Gordon Edward, 1854-1925
Sherman, Isaac, 1753-1819
Sherman, John, 1750-1802
Sherman, Oliver, 1777-1820
Sherman, Roger, 1768-1856
Sherman, Roger Minott>, 1773-1844
Sherrill, Charles Hitchcock, 1867-1936
Shipley, (Howard) Maynard, 1872-1934
Shipman, William Davis, 1818-1898
Sill, Edward Rowland, 1841-1887
Sill, George Griswald, 1829-1907
Silliman, Benjamin, 1779-1864
Silliman, Benjamin, 1816-1885
Silliman, Benjamin D., 1805-1901
Silliman, Gold Selleck, 1777-1868
Simonds, William Edgar, 1842-1903
(Skinner, Chloe (Sherman), 1758-1840)
Skinner, Harriet (Backus), 1805-1885
Skinner, Roger Sherman, 1795-1838
Smith, Alfred Emanuel, 1874-1944
Smith, Charles Edward, 1847-1880
Smith, Edward Alan, 1857-1928
Smith, Edwin Burritt, Â -1906
Smith, Isaac, Â -1929
Smith, John Cotton, 1765-1845
Smith, Nathan, 1762-1829
Smith, Nathan, 1770-1835
Smith, Nathan Ryns, 1797-1877
Smith, Nathaniel, 1762-1822
Smith, Nathaniel Benedict, 1795-1881
Smith, Ralph Dunning, 1804-1874
Smith, Truman, 1791-1884
Smith, William Nathan Horvell, 1812-1889
Smyth, Egbert Coffin, 1829-1904
Soule, Charles Carroll, 1842-1913
Southwick, Elbridge G. 1842-Â
Southworth, Edward Wells, 1854-1902
Sparks, Jared, 1789-1866
Speer, Emory, 1848-1918
Sperry, Lewis, 1848-1922
Sperry, Nehemiah Day, 1827-1911
Sprague, Peleg, 1793-1880
Sprague, William Buell, 1795-1876
Spring, Gardiner, 1785-1873
Spring, Samuel, 1792-1877
Squier, Ephraim George, 1821-1888
Stanton, George Howard, 1867-1941
Stanton, Lewis Elliot, 1833-1916
Staples, Seth Perkins, 1776-1861
Staples, Sophos, 1789-1826
Starkey, Stephen William, 1797-1864
Stayton, William H., 1861-1942
Stearns, Ezra Scollay, 1838-Â
Stebbins, Stephen William, 1758-1843
Steiner, Lewis Henry, 1827-1892
Steinwehr, Adolph Wilhelm August Friedrich Baron von, 1822-1877
Sterling, George Loomis, 1855-1913
Sterne, Simon, 1839-1901
Stevens, Byan Kerby, 1792-1870
Stevens, George Barker, 1854-1906
Stevens, Henry, 1819-1886
Stewart, John Aikman, 1822-1926
Stewart, William Morris, 1827-1909
Stimson, Henry Albert, 1842-1936
Stimson, Henry Lewis, 1867-1950
Stockbridge, Henry Smith, 1822-1895
Stoddard, Henry, 1843-1941
Stoddard, Louis Ezekiel, 1878-1948
Stoddert, Benjamin, 1751-1813
Stone, William Leete, 1792-1844
Stover, Bellamy, 1798-1875
Storey, Moorfield, 1845-1929
Storrs, Richard Salter, 1821-1900
Storrs, William Lucius, 1795-1961
Stoughton, John Alden, 1848-1915
Stowe, Orson William, Â -1883
Stowe, Calvin Ellis, 1802-1886
Stowe, Harriet Elizabeth (Beecher), 1811-1896
Straus, Oscar Solomon, 1850-1926
Street, Robert Gould, 1843-Â
Strong, Cyprian, 1743-1811
Strong, Joseph, 1770-1812
Strong, Josiah, 1847-1916
Strong, Selah, 1795-Â
Strong, Selah Brewster, 1792-1872
Strong, William B. 1808-1895
Sturges, Lewis Burr, 1763-1844
Sugita, Kinnosuke, 1859-1933
Sulzer, William, 1863-1941
Sumner, William Graham, 1840-1910
Swan, Charles Walter, 1838-Â
Swift, Zephaniah, 1759-1823
Taft, William Howard, 1857-1930
Talbot, Richmond, Â -1887
Talcott, John Carlos, 1857-1904
Talcott, Mary Kingsbury, 1847-1917
Talcott, Thadeus Mead, 1875-Â
Tallmadge, James, 1778-1853
Tappan, James Camp, 1825-1906
Tappan, Lewis, 1788-1873
Tarbox, Increase Niles, 1815-1888
Taussig, Frank William, 1859-1940
Taylor, Hannis, 1851-1922
Taylor, Robert Stewart, 1838-1918
Taylor, Zachary, 1784-1850
Terry, George Edward, 1836-Â
Terry, Henry Taylor, 1847-1936
Thacher, James Kingsley, 1847-1891
Thacher, Sherman Day, 1861-1913
Thacher, Thomas Anthony, 1815-1886
Thacher, Thomas Anthony, 1887-Â
Thayer, Amos Madden, 1841-1905
Thayer, James Bradley, 1831-1902
Thayer, William Roscoe, 1859-1923
Thayer, John Mowry, 1847-1924
Thomas, John, 1792-1866
Thompson, Curtis, Â -1904
Thorn, Sophia Lord, Â -1905
Thornton, William, 1759-1828
Thorpe, Francis Newton, 1857-1926
Thwing, Charles Franklin, 1853-1937
Titsworth, John 1793-1873
Todd, Charles Stewart, 1791-1871
Todd, John Edwards, 1833-1907
Tomlinson, Charles, 1837-1921
Tomlinson, Gideon, 1780-1854
Tomlinson, Joseph, 1828-1901
Torrance, David, 1840-1906
Torrey, George Arnold, -1864
Totten, Joseph Gilbert, 1788-
Toucey, Isaac, 1792-1869
Tourjee, Eben, 1834-1891
Town, Ithiel, 1784-1844
Townsend, Amos, Â -1885
Townsend, James Mulford, 1825-1901
Townsend, William Kneedland, 1848-1907
Tracy, Elisha, 1766-1842
Tracy, Jeremiah Evarts, 1835-1923
Tracy, Uriah, 1755-1807
Train, Abner, Leavenworth, 1830-1891
Treadway, Francis Wilcox, 1869-1925
Troup, Alexander, Â -1908
Troup, Philip, 1878-1936
Trowbridge, Rutherford, 1851-Â
Trowbridge, Thomas Rutherford, 1810-1887
Trowbridge, William Petit, 1828-1892
Trudeau, Edward Livingston, 1848-1915
Trumbull, Benjamin, 1735-1820
Trumbull, David, 1819-1889
Trumbull, John, 1756-1843
Trumbull, Jonathan, 1710-1785
Trumbull, Jonathan, 1740-1809
Trumbull, Joseph, 1782-1861
Trumbull, Lymna, 1813-1896
Trumbull, William, 1861-1933
Tsachiga, Loichi, 1867-1890
Tucker, Henry St. George, 1853-Â
Tucker, John Randolph, 1823-1897
Tucker, William Jewett, 1839-1926
Turner, Frederick Jackson, 1861-1932
Twichell, Joseph Hopkins, 1838-1918
Twining, Alexander Catlin, 1801-1884
Twining, Kingley, 1832-1901
Tyler, Daniel Putnam, 1798-1875
Tyler, Edwin, 1827-1868
Tyler, Morris Franklin, 1848-1907
Tyler, Septimus, 1789-1817
Tyner, Richard Henry, 1866-1914
Ullman, Jacob Bertram, 1870-1906
Upson, Henry, 1831-1911
Vaill, Joseph, 1790-1869
Van Buren, Martin, 1782-1862
Vande Graaff, Adrian Sebastian, 1859-1922
Van Devanter, Willis, 1859-1941
Van Renssalaer, Soloman, 1774-1852
Van Schaick, George Slingerland, 1883-Â
Van Vechten, Teunis, 1785-1859
Vaux, Richard, 1816-1895
Vinal, Charles Green Rich, 1840-Â
Wait, John Turner, 1811-1899
Wakeman, Burr, 1795-1888
Wakeman, Stephen Hubbel, 1793-1863
Wales, George Washington, Â -1896
Wales, Leonard Eugene, 1788-1823
Wales, Leonard Eugene, 1823-1897
Walker, Albert Henry, 1844-1915
Walker, Francis Amasa, 1840-1897
Walker, Williston, 1860-1922
Walley, Henshaw Bates, Â -1913
Walsh, David Agnatius, 1872-1947
Walworth, Reuben Hyde, 1788-1867
Wambaugh, Eugene, 1856-1940
Ward, William Hayes, 1835-1916
Warner, Aaron Edward, 1839-1884
Warner, Levi, 1830-Â
Warren, William Fairfield, 1833-1929
Washburn, Emory, 1800-1877
Watson, Thomas Landsell, 1847-Â
Wayland, Francis, 1826-1904
Webb, Henry L., 1795-1876
Webster, Noah, 1758-1843
Weeden, William Babcock, 1834-1912
Weeks, John Wingate, 1860-1926
Weir, John Ferguson, 1841-1926
Welch, Archibald Achley, 1859-1935
Wells, Philip Patterson, 1868-Â
West, Nathaniel, 1748-1815
Wharton, Francis, 1820-1889
Wheeler, Albert Sproull, 1833-1905
Wheeler, Arthur Martin, 1835-1918
Wheeler, David Everett, 1804-1870
Wheeler, George Wakeman, 1860-1932
Whitney, Edward Baldwin, 1857-1911
White, Andrew Dickson, 1832-1918
White, Edward Douglas, 1845-1921
White, Henry Charles, 1856-1914
Whitelock, George, 1854-1920
Whiton, James Horris, 1833-1920
Whittlesey, Elisha, 1783-1863
Wightman, Stillman King, 1803-1899
Wigmore, John Henry, 1863-1943
Wilcox, Eljen Kossuth, -1914
Wilfley, Lebbeus Redman, 1866-1926
Willard, James Lawrence, 1825-1894
Willard, Joseph, 1798-1865
Willard, Samuel George, 1819-1887
Williams, John, 1817-1899
Williams, Thomas Scott, 1777-1861
Williams, Thomas Wheeler, 1789-1874
Willoughby, Westel Woodbury, 1867-1945
Willson, Augustus Everett, 1846-1931
Wilson, George Grafton, 1863-1951
Wilson, James Harrison, 1837-1925
Wilson, John Done, 1833-1908
Wilson, William Lyne, 1843-1900
Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924
Winchester, Stephen Stearns, 1834-1880
Winthrop, Buchanan, 1841-1900
Wolcott, Alexander, 1780-Â
Wolcott, Frederick, 1767-1837
Woodbridge, William, 1780-1861
Woodruff, Clinton Roger, 1868-Â
Woodruff, George Catlin, 1805-1885
Woodruff, Rollin Simmons, 1854-Â
Woodward, Bezaleel, 1745-1804
Woodward, Thomas Green, 1788-1849
Woodworth, John, 1768-1858
Woolsey, Theodore Dwight, 1801-1889
Woolsey, Theodore Salisbury, 1852-1829
Woolworth, James Mills, 1829-1906
Wooster, William Burr, 1821-1900
Worcester, Edwin Dean, 1856-1929
Worcester, Joseph Emerson, 1784-1865
Wright, Arthur Williams, 1836-1915
Wright, Dexter Russel, 1821-1886
Wright, Elizun, 1761-1845
Wright, Henry Parks, 1839-1918
Wright, Robert William, 1816-1885
Wright, Silas, 1795-1847
Wurts, John, 1855-1936
Wynn, William Jefferson, 1876-Â
Yardley, Henry Albert, 1834-1882
Yeaman, George Helm, 1829-1908